And then you watch the footage that they
wouldn't release during the trials and
you see them getting a guided tour.
>> Yeah. And as it turns out, the only one
who was actually plotting to overthrow
the government was John Brennan.
>> It's just so gross that
>> Yeah.
>> their our legal system gets used against
political opponents in that way in such
a devious and just a sinister way.
Joe Rogan and CIA whistleblower John
Kiryaku just exposed the truth about
January 6th. What the feds hid from the
public in that narrative, how involved
the FBI was in that story and in that
entrapment scheme and what we can learn
about it now. So, let's get right into
it. Please like the video and subscribe
to the channel.
>> Jim Gaffin was talking about what they
did in January 6. I go, "Do you
understand that there were paid people
that were working for the federal
government? There were employees of the
federal government that were on that
lawn trying to convince people to go
in." And he was very incredulous.
He He did He did not believe it. And I
said, "They are Asian provocators that
are that is their job to try to get you
to do something illegal."
>> Exactly. So they can build their careers
by making these arrests. Not just that,
but demonize the president, the former
president to a much larger extent
>> to charge him with insurrection to say
that he was plotting to overthrow the
government.
>> Yeah. And as it turns out, the only one
who was actually plotting to overthrow
the government was John Brennan.
>> Oh man, isn't that the truth? That's
pretty base, but that's true. John
Brennan, one of the chief architects of
Russia gate, the dualpurpose scheme,
propaganda scheme by the deep state to
undermine the sitting president and
frame him for treason, for specious
reasons. And guess what? I think there
are a lot of bad things about Trump. But
that was a specious charge and
antagonize Russia at the same time.
That's exactly right. FBI informants
entrap dissident all the time. This one
had the dual purpose of undermining the
president and saying that there's an
insurrection, leading with that
insurrection narrative we couldn't stop
hearing about until it became more and
more apparent to people actually paying
attention that the feds orchestrated
this entire thing.
>> There was this fundamental
misunderstanding of what an operations
officer was supposed to do. An
operations officer goes out and collects
intelligence and then sends it back and
that's it. Then it's up to the analyst
to decide this is great, this is crap,
this is not true, this is a partially
true, whatever. So he goes out there,
talks to whatever low-level terrible
sources he happen to have, writes all
this nonsense down, sends it back, and
they're like, "Look what Donald Trump
did. He hired prostitutes to pee on
Barack Obama's bed." No, he didn't.
One guy made this up and Christopher
Steel wrote it and sent it back. That
doesn't make it fact.
>> Wasn't it funded by the Hillary Clinton?
>> It sure was.
>> Yeah. The Steel Dossier started off as
an adversarial investigative
program by the Democrats to try to
undermine Trump, try to, you know, drag
him into this Russian conspiracy where
he was colluding with Putin and the deep
state. The CIA and FBI just latched on
to that, took a hold of it and it
entrapped the US mindset for two to
three years. At least on the legacy
media, all we heard was that this is,
you know, deeper than Watergate. This is
the biggest political scandal in US
history we have on our hands where Trump
is essentially acting as a Putin
collaborator within the federal
government. It all turned about out to
be bogus and nuts. And they still had to
sell this while Trump was slapping
sanctions on Russia. He was complaining
that Russia had given Snowden safe
haven. He had withdrawn from the INF
treaty. And he gave Ukraine offensive
weapons in the form of $400 million
worth of dualpurpose offensive weapons
for the first time. And they still led
with this narrative and captivated a lot
of people with it.
>> Yes, it was.
>> Yeah.
>> Which is equally wild.
>> You made another point. I wanted to
address these January 6 people.
Let's say that some of them
did do whatever, broke the window or
went into the building unauthorized.
Okay, then that's deserving of a smack
on the hand and and a strongly worded
letter and maybe a $1,000 fine. Don't do
that again. Well, even that to me
represents a perversion of the original
republic where if you're going to call
this the people's house, the people have
the right to be in that house or protest
around those grounds, especially when
Capitol Hill police are letting them in.
But yeah, he's making a good point. I
mean, that's not an insurrection. These
people weren't armed, but that's what
they went with. That's what they said
that this was an attempt to throw a coup
over the federal government despite the
fact that Trump said, you know, don't be
violent. It It's just so absurd. And I
have many reasons to dislike Trump.
Can't stand Trump. You guys know that.
But this one was absurd.
>> 30 years in prison.
Again, is society really better off by
locking all these people up and spending
millions and millions of dollars of the
taxpayers money to do it?
>> Of course not.
>> No, of course not. But it it also just
divides us even further. It does. And it
also ve very much distorted the
narrative with people like Jim Gaffigan
who's a friend of mine who's a very
left-leaning comedian and he had it in
his mind that these people went and they
al they also have this thing where they
say a cop was murdered,
>> right?
>> That's not true.
>> I hate that
>> they say it over and over again. That's
not true. One cop died after the fact of
a heart attack. it. You could say maybe
it was because of the stress of January
6th. Perhaps
>> maybe, maybe not.
>> Maybe not.
>> Maybe.
>> Yeah. And that's the murder narrative
that they led with instead of, hey, the
only person that actually was murdered
that day was a protester, Ashley Babbot.
Rest in peace, by the way. Murdered by
Capitol Hill police. But this was
somehow still an insurrection, an
unarmed insurrection in which no member
of the federal government was killed by
the protesters. It's absolutely absurd.
They ran wild with this. You had AOC
saying that, you know, she feared for
her life. They got into Pelos's office
and this is, you know, violating the
statist
kind of sacred pulpit. They view the
capital as some kind of religious
institution that it should not be viewed
as. Especially in today's day and age
where the government is so completely
corrupt, they view this as violative of,
you know, the most sacred sacrament of
their civil religion, the US capital.
It's just so absurd.
>> He shouldn't have been a cop.
>> Yeah. I mean, if you can significant
health problems,
>> right? Like that's not normal to just
die of a heart attack because of a very
stressful day.
>> Mhm. That's but that's it. This idea
that they killed cops that keep that
narrative keeps coming out. It was an
insurrection. They murdered cops. They
broke into the White House. They were
looking for Nancy Pelosi. They were
going to kill her. Like, okay, are you
sure? Because there's a lot of this
story that's [__] Now, it turns out
at one point in time, they were saying
it was 20 FBI agents. Now, the the
latest number is 270.
>> That's right.
>> Yeah.
>> That's huge.
>> That's a lot of people. It's a lot of
people that are encouraging people to
break in.
>> And there's many instances of these
suspected people that are on camera. A
lot of them are wearing face masks. Um
there's one of them where a guy's
removing the broken glass from the
window and encouraging people to go in
and another guy gets in his faces and
goes, "Do not do that." And then he
pushes that guy, "Fuck you." And the
other guy backs off.
Um,
how is that not
being investigated as a serious crime?
Because the FBI isn't going to
investigate itself. The FBI is the
problem. That's the nature of the deep
state. They get away with all sorts of
crimes that regular people could not get
away with. They cover for their own and
they always make excuses. This goes far
deeper than Ray Apps. He said there were
something like 270 known FBI assets in
the crowd that day. Yeah, it might not
be all of them saying, you know, go into
the capital, but that's what Ray Ep
said. That's what Nick Fuentes said from
a megaphone on the side. I don't know.
You know, I don't have the proof in
front of me that these were FBI
informants. But both of those men had a
bullhorn, said to do things like that,
and then they themselves did not do that
thing that they called for others to do.
But it goes far beyond that. It it is
entrenched in the FBI system for these
assets to entrap people in schemes that
they wouldn't engage in without that
agitation by these deep state actors
that just get away with it. They're
criminals of the highest degree. And the
criminals aren't going to investigate
the criminals. And whenever they pretend
to investigate the criminals, it's the
government investigating the government
and determining that the government did
nothing wrong. And like that that is a
serious
it's a violation of what you're supposed
to be doing in the first place. If the
FBI was on that loan on that lawn, I
would hope what they would be doing is
informing people entering into this
building is a felony. Breaking these
windows, getting into this building is
you do not want to do this. If you want
to peacefully protest, do that. But I'm
telling you, this will [__] with you for
the rest of your life. and most likely
ruin it.
>> Yeah, I'm with Joe. I wish that was the
case, too. But that's a very idealistic
bluepilled way to look at the world. The
hypothetical
environment in which the FBI would
actually do that. Yeah. If we lived in a
just society, I would like that, but
that's utterly delusional. If people
think that that is actually what the FBI
is going to be, even if you reform it,
the FBI doesn't exist to protect us. The
FBI exists to destroy the lives of
dissident, kill the innocents. That's
what Ruby Ridge and Waco prove. That's
what the murder of Fred Hampton prove.
The wiretapping under co-intel pro and
people like Stokeley Carmichael and
Martin Luther King and Malcolm X. That's
what that proved. And this is no
different. The FBI is villainous. It
deserves to be abolished completely. No
ifs, ands, or buts, no reform. I think
you're 100% right.
>> That's what I would hope from law
enforcement. I wouldn't hope that they
would be trying to set people up
>> and from a civil society,
>> right?
>> You know, do we we want to set people up
to go to prison? We want to wreck
families and wreck people's lives. Why
would we want to do that?
>> Also,
what was there? Did they turn down the
idea of bringing in the National Guard?
>> You know, I I really don't understand.
It appears Yes, it it appears that
that's exactly what happened.
>> Could also significantly deterred people
from committing these crimes.
>> That's right.
>> That they were encouraged to do.
>> I'll tell you, if I was at a
demonstration and all of a sudden the
National Guard showed up, I'd say, "Ah,
this isn't for me." Yeah.
>> Yeah. And I think most people would do
that as well.
>> Agreed. But to be truthful here, I the
government ran with the narrative that
they didn't turn off the idea of the
National Guard coming in. They said it
was just completely delayed, which that
doesn't meet withstand scrutiny in some
stretches that the National Guard
couldn't have been mobilized. But that
is the narrative that they went with
that they didn't turn down the presence
of the National Guard. They were just
too delayed to make a serious presence
known on January 6th, right?
It's crazy. It's just so gross that
Yeah.
>> their our legal system gets used against
political opponents in that way in such
a devious and just a sinister way.
>> Harry Truman once famously said, "If you
want a friend in Washington, get a dog."
[Laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. God, what a gross business.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And it's been going on a
long time since the inception of the
FBI. The FBI, you know, established by
its chief architect. I mean, the Bureau
of Investigation had existed beforehand,
but Jay Edgar Hoover was big on
warrantless wiretapping and extracting
blackmail from people in power such that
they wouldn't do anything about his
power. That's what COINTIel Pro was. It
was an attempt to undermine the lives of
dissident in America, especially during
the civil rights era. A lot of the black
nationalists, a lot of the black civil
rights attorneys and civil rights
activists had their rights completely
perverted by this sinister regime for
doing things that weren't illegal and
doing things to them that again would be
illegal if it was me or you doing that.
The government has a different standard
than you and me. Which throws a lot of
kind of reputation against this idea
that the government's just a reflection
of us. That the government exists based
on the consent of the govern. No one in
the govern agreed that they should have
that power. And that's a power that the
public couldn't delegate to them cuz we
ourselves don't have the power to
destroy innocent lives like that. to
rummage through the personal
conversations and effects of others and
to in Martin Luther King's case try to
convince him to commit suicide. By the
way, deputy director of the FBI William
Sullivan drafted a memo trying to
convince him to do that. Many people
still don't know that, but that letter
was divulged. It's been declassified and
you can see that now. It's just sad
because I also am a patriot and I want
to think of us as better than that.
>> Yeah, we're the good guys. And I don't
think it's necessarily the fault of
these individuals. I think the system
really sucks. And I think you work for
that system and just like all these
Congress people that wind up insider
trading, everybody else is doing it.
It's the culture. You get wrapped up in
it. Just like bad cops, you know, you
get assigned to a precinct that's filled
with corrupt cops and you have to do
things to stay with them. They're your
blood brothers and you're all in this
together. And so you wind up doing some
criminal activities that you think are
just everybody does it. This is what we
do.
>> Yep.
>> And you're an FBI agent. Well, we got to
set this guy up. Okay, let's set him up.
This is what we do. Hey, if he doesn't
do it, he's not committing a crime. We
got nothing on him. Okay.
>> And then you just convince him to do it.
And he's a [__] idiot. And so he does
it and he hits that cell phone and now
you're arresting him and he's like,
"What?"
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. As far as where the culpability
lies, it is a systematic issue. No
doubt. this is a perverted toxic
political apparatus under which we live.
But also, if you're taking away the
culpability of individuals knowing that
this is what they do, I think that's not
appropriating the responsibility
correctly completely either because
that's the SS defense. We are just
following orders. And that's not to say
people's, you know, earnest feelings
about what they're getting into aren't
perverted by the system itself. But at
the point you realize that, it behooves
you to resign. Same thing with the
military. You know, even if it's a
dishonorable discharge, that would ruin,
you know, your ability to hold rights in
some regards, that probably is more
moral um to take accountability for
that, to go against the perverted war
machine than to suffer, you know, having
to kill other people in the name of the
state, in the name of Israel, in the
name of Ukraine, or whatever proxy war
or regime change war the US happens to
be dealing with at that time. And he's
so dumb. He barely knows what happened.
>> Mhm. And the chances are he can't afford
a decent attorney or he's not notorious
enough and newsworthy enough to to get,
you know, A-list attorneys volunteering
pro bono, right?
>> So, he's stuck with a a public defender
that's going to spend eight hours on the
case and he's going to get screwed in
the end.
>> And there's also the narrative that's
very difficult to shake. So if you get
accused of some sort of a heinous crime,
the narrative for most people that are
casual viewers of that story is that
you're a terrorist. Yeah.
>> Or you're a guy who's going to kidnap
the governor or you're a guy who is an
insurrectionist who's trying to
overthrow the government on January 6th.
And then you watch the footage that they
wouldn't release during the trials and
you see them getting a guided tour, the
guided tour through through like the the
security guards are walking them into
the Senate. Like what the [__] What is
this?
>> Like what is and why is no one outraged?
And why is it only one side that's
outraged? God, if I was a a if I was a a
a Democrat congressman or a senator or
if I was any sort of a politician on the
other side, I'd be like, do you know how
disgusting this is?
>> This is you're you're using this to go
after Donald Trump of all things in
instead of just better political
opposition.
>> Exactly.
Yeah, they don't want that. They want
supreme power and coercion. And yeah,
Tucker Carlson was heroic for releasing
that footage of January 6. The regime
did not want them releasing that
footage, showing the guided tour,
showing people peacefully walking, you
know, through filed lines and orderly
lines through the capital on that day,
being led in there by Capitol Hill
police. And look, I don't think a lot of
Americans know this because of how we've
been, you know, groomed, how we've been
raised, what we've been taught, the
propaganda that comes through us, you
know, as we go into government schools.
But, you know, people could go into the
White House, people could approach the
White House, people could ring the White
House door, you know, as late as the
Harding presidency. I think a lot of
that changed during the Wilson
presidency, but this was really uh you
know the people's not Congress but the
White House. But the same was true of
Congress. Congress wasn't just this
locked down imperial like sanctum. This
locked down imperial bastion of power in
which it was locked down by the national
security regime. Not until much much
later. Same thing with the White House.
So, if you're going to say again, this
is the people's house, the people have a
right to it, and they weren't exactly
armed. They weren't dangerous. It turns
out the Capitol Hill police were more
dangerous. But this isn't the only
entrapment the FBI engages in. There's
been many more things. Here's one
example. The Whitmer entrapment plot. If
you remember this from 2020, the feds
said, "Hey, you know, these eventually I
think they charged something like nine
people were involved in this plot to
surveil and then kidnap the governor of
Michigan, Gretchen Whitmer. She still is
today." And defense attorneys said,
"Hey, this was FBI assetbased coercion
where these guys were entrapped because
they might have had, you know, some
animosities toward her for other issues
and then they were goated along by
federal agents to get involved with
this. Now, in this case, some of them
were convicted and some of them were
acquitted. In another case, in 2012, we
had this Cleveland Bridge, the 82 bridge
incident. If many people remember this
one, this is where there were some guys
basically drinking in a bar essentially
drunk. And those guys were in trap, too.
there happened to be an FBI agent or an
asset, one of the two on the scene, you
know, goating them into giving them
explosives to blow up this bridge,
saying, "Hey, you know, you guys should
blow up this bridge." And they're like,
"Yeah, I guess so." You know, and they
bought some explosives that weren't even
remotely enough to actually blow up that
bridge. So, this is not a new issue.
This has been happening a long time.
It's been happening recently in these
three cases. We know that's true. And
FBI enttrapment is just another reason
why the FBI must be eliminated, not be
reformed, not be like cut down to size
by firing something like 200 people. And
this Trump drain the swamp mentality
should actually be applied to the FBI,
not just be rhetoric that was used as an
electoral vehicle because if you
remember Cash Patel said, "Hey, my goal
is to shut down the Hoover building and
then replace it with a museum to the
deep state." Well, guess what happened?
That didn't happen. That's what I can
say. But FBI enttrapment is a serious
issue. This was one of the most loony
narratives that the feds sold and sold
largely successfully for a few years
that this unarmed protest in which there
were some riots, there were some
breaking of windows and things like
that. A lot of it antagonized by the
federal assets there, led on by Capitol
Hill police, but was not an
insurrection, was unarmed, had no
wherewithal to overthrow the federal
government. and no wherewithal to change
what congressional votes would be that
day. It's just so stupid. The whole
thing was a Looney Tunes narrative. And
of course, that's what CNN and MS NBC
carried for several years. Thankfully,
many Americans know better now. Some
people still claim that that was an
insurrection. But I think you should
look at them as if they're saying like,
"Hey, you know, I you you guys saw what
you saw. You can say what you want, but
you know, Chris Christie is actually an
aerobic, you know, super athlete. He's
not fat like you say. He's not fat like
you see. He's actually a super athlete
and you guys need to acknowledge that.
But that's where we're at. But I do want
to hear from you. Do you agree with John
Kiryaku on Joe Rogan about this FBI
entrament? What's the truth about
January 6? Let me know in the comments
down below. Please like the video,
subscribe to the channel, subscribe to
Joe Rogan. Excellent interview. John
Kiyaku is a hero. He is a CIA
whistleblower that blew the whistle on
US torture against, you know, suspected
terrorists and served time in jail for
that. Total hero. Deserves a complete
pardon. Will never get one, but should
get one because he exposed crimes that
even the US Constitution prohibits. No
um no torture. You can't do that under
the US Constitution. But let me know
what you think. Um, if you like this
video and other videos like it that I
do, please consider becoming a YouTube
member by clicking the join button
below. You can help support this
channel. And if you do that, I will
thank you profusely. And in return for
that good deed on your side, I'll give
you access to all my videos before they
go live to the general public on
YouTube. And until I see you guys next
time, no more war, no more debt, no more
inflation, and no more empire. Peace
out, guys. Catch you in the next one.